《指定幸存者》前情提要
Previously on "Designated Survivor"...
我希望我的女儿能够看到一位女性
I would like my daughter to see a woman
成为了美利坚合众国的副总统
become vice president.
谢谢  先生
Thank you, sir.
道德委员会刚刚宣布
The House Ethics Committee,
他们要展开对议长的调查
they are opening an investigation into the Speaker.
他是个伟大的总统
My dad was a great president.
泰勒  对你的丧亲之痛我非常遗憾
Tyler, I am sorry for your incredible loss.
洛萨诺还活着  先生
Lozano is alive, sir.
联调局击毙的人是个替身
The man the FBI killed was a decoy.
杰伊·惠特克  国土安全部顾问
Jay Whitaker, Homeland Security Adviser.
洛萨诺是个很厉害的士兵
Lozano was a total soldier.
我很高兴我们抓到了这个混蛋
I'm just glad we caught the son of a bitch.
我也是
Me too.
我们已经知道白宫里有人
We've known that someone in the White House
想让柯克曼成为指定幸存者
made Kirkman designated survivor.
这个人可能还活着
This person may still be active.
杰森  我需要你的帮助
Hey, Jason. I need your help.
要我干什么
What do you need?
帕特里克·劳埃德
Patrick Lloyd.
怎么样了
How'd it go?
非常顺利
Clockwork.
我们重回正轨了
We're back on track.
很高兴我们能有机会深入研究这个
I'm glad we had a chance to dig in on this.
我也是
Me, too.
如果我们能够在不影响安全的情况下
If we can expedite TSA screenings
加快安检速度
without sacrificing security,
这钱就花得值得
it's money well-spent.
总统就希望能提高人民的生活质量
And the president is all about making people's lives easier.
我们或许可以在北约峰会之后
Perhaps we can put this on his radar
向他提出来
after the NATO summit?
在此期间你会给我需要的数据吧
In the meantime, you'll get me that data?
-成交  -很好
- Consider it done. - Great.
包裹已发出
指定幸存者
第一季 第十九集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我刚来白宫的时候
So, here's something I didn't know
还不知道这件事
when I came to the White House.
翻译     Michael  潇然  星星与野狗  酥ki酱
乔治·华盛顿在独立战争期间
George Washington ran America's first spy ring
组建了美国第一个间谍网
during the Revolutionary War.
翻译     胡说大王  一只虾  长颈鹿   silence
他的特工们传递了英国军队的动向
His agents relayed British troop movements.
当时连电话都还没有呢
And they didn't even have cellphones.
翻译     pang  子V  桃子  MQ小早  尼基塔
他看起来不太高兴
He doesn't look very happy.
如果你也戴着木质假牙
Well, you probably wouldn't want to smile either
校对     长颈鹿  潇然
大概就不会想笑了吧
if you had wooden teeth.
-总统先生  -总统来了
- Mr. President! - It's the President!
我听说今天有一群特殊的客人
I heard that we had some very special guests
时间轴     壬虚浪影  Avis  姜姜
来了白宫
here in the White House today.
包括里士满总统的儿子
Including President Richmond's son.
泰勒  很高兴再次见到你
Tyler, really good to see you again.
后期     虫虫不咬人
我也是  总统先生
Same here, Mr. President.
请容我介绍来自新奥尔良的
Allow me to introduce the student orchestra of
总监     MQ小早
罗伯特·里士满高中的学生管弦乐队
Robert Richmond High School in New Orleans.
很荣幸见到大家
It is an honor to meet all of you,
我听到传闻说
and I heard a rumor that we're gonna get to hear
公告     人人影视永久官方网站 www.YYeTs.com
今天下午能听到你们的表演
you perform later this afternoon.
我也听到了
I heard that rumor, too.
我已经等不及了
Can't wait to hear it.
如果有任何需要
And if there's anything you need,
请不要犹豫直说就行
please don't hesitate to ask.
请讲
Yes?
能跟您合张影吗
Can I take a picture with you?
我很荣幸  来吧
It would be my pleasure. Come on.
谢谢您的支持  总统先生
Thank you for doing this, Mr. President.
你这是什么话
Are you kidding?
李奥和佩妮去了总统行宫
With Leo and Penny up in Camp David,
白宫里又能迎来些孩子挺好的
well, it's nice to have young people in the White House again.
看到你与这些学生分享
It's great to see you sharing your passion for music
对音乐的热情真好
with these students.
不敢当
Oh, well, I can't take credit.
这个团队其实是一个全国性项目的一部分
This group is actually part of a national program
这个项目资助公立学校的艺术教育
that funds the arts in public schools.
那挺不错
Oh, that's wonderful.
但遗憾的是
And, unfortunately,
这个项目要终止了
it, um, might all come to an end.
国会批准提供资金的时候
You see, when the funding was approved,
设定了"日落条款"
Congress put in a sunset clause,
对计划规定失效日期
到期后除非再次得到批准  否则就此失效
因此拨款每五年要更新一次
so the grant has to be renewed every five years.
-什么时候到期  -下个月
- When's it expire? - Next month.
所以这可能就结束了
So, this might be the end of playing music
很多孩子的音乐路
for a lot of these kids,
他们很多人家里支付不起私人课程
and, you know, most of their families can't afford private lessons.
我家当时也付不起
Mine couldn't either.
我当年在小学乐团里吹小号
I played trumpet in my elementary school band.
我都不知道您参与过演奏
Oh, I didn't know you played.
我都没法说那叫演奏
Well, I wouldn't exactly call it playing.
事实上  我吹得特别烂
In fact, it was pretty awful.
但重要的是那段经历
But it was the experience that mattered.
我非常赞同
That -- I-I -- couldn't agree more.
音乐构成了我的全部生活
Music shaped my whole life.
李奥也对音乐很痴迷
Leo's all about it, too.
不过我得承认
But I have to admit,
我可能无法体会到电子音乐的魅力所在
I don't think I can get into dubstep.
这可不一定
Hey, you never know.
我爸向我介绍了勃拉姆斯
My dad introduced me to Brahms,
德国古典音乐作曲家
而我让他迷上了电台司令[摇滚乐队]
I got him hooked on Radiohead.
我向你保证  我会跟进拨款的事
I promise you. I will look into the grant.
谢谢您  先生
Thank you, sir.
我知道这种小事
I know this is small stuff
跟您手上的事情比太微不足道了
compared to everything else you've got going on --
不  不  这不是小事
No, no, it's not small stuff.
这个国家的所有学生
I think every student in this country
都应该有机会接受艺术方面的熏陶
should have access to the arts for their education.
我很荣幸能帮上忙
It'll be an honor to help.
-那我们演奏会见  -我都等不及了
- I'll see you at the concert? - I can't wait.
我查了她所有的文件
I went through all of her files.
大部分都和布朗宁·里德有关
Most of them have to do with Browning Reed.
也许她出外勤了  所以要关闭无线电联络
Maybe she's out in the field and had to go radio silent.
也许吧
Yeah, maybe.
你看
Look, you know,
我知道威尔士不怎么按常理出牌
I know Wells isn't exactly by-the-book, right?
但她要是在查什么  肯定会告诉我的
But, if she working something, she would've let me know.
那杰森·亚特伍德呢
What about Jason Atwood?
她不是带杰森一起去的北达科他州
I mean, she did bring him to North Dakota with her, right?
也许  也许他们俩联系了
Maybe -- maybe he's talked to her.
我已经问了  他什么都不知道
I already tried. He doesn't know anything.
况且  汉娜告诉过我她不想让他插手
Besides, Hannah told me she sidelined him anyway.
她住哪
Where's she staying?
这就是她的车
This is her.
去她房间里看看
Let's check her room.
抱歉打扰  女士
Excuse me, ma'am?
特勤局
Secret Service.
能帮我们开门吗
Would you open this door, please?
有任何发现吗
Anything?
没有
No.
她已经走了
She's gone.
检查下安保监控录像
Let's check the security cameras.
抱歉
Sorry.
要看路啊
Hey, eyes on the road!
抱歉  霍斯拉滕的道德委员听证会要开始了
Sorry, Hookstraten's Ethics Committee hearing's about to start.
至少我知道媒体在今天的简报里
Well, at least I know what the press is gonna ask me about
会问我什么了
in today's briefing.
所有人都爱听道德丑闻
Everybody loves an ethics scandal,
尤其是关于副总统的流言
especially given the V.P. rumors.
所谓副总统的流言都只是流言而已  赛斯
The V.P. rumors are just that, Seth. Rumors.
这里可是华盛顿
This is Washington.
事情总能有巧妙的方法变为现实
Things have a tricky way of becoming reality.
就等着看听证会怎么样吧
Let's just see how this hearing goes.
你还没评价我的新发型呢
Hey! You didn't say anything about my haircut.
看起来不错
Yeah, it looks good.
你都没注意到呢
You didn't even notice.
看起来都一样
I mean, it looks the same?
一如既往的好
It always looks great.
怎么  剪了吗
What is -- what?
为这次出差剪的
I got it for the trip.
我都没意识到参加北约峰会能让你如此激动
Wow, I didn't realize you were so excited for a NATO summit.
不  不是为了北约峰会
No, not for NATO.
我要在空军一号[总统专机]里拍很多照片
I figure I'll be taking a lot of pictures on Air Force One.
你之前坐过飞机的吧
Um, you've been on a -- a plane before, right?
但没有坐过空军一号啊
Ooh, not this one.
我的天
Oh, my God.
众议院道德委员会
我和我的同事在此将判定
What my colleagues and I are here to determine is
你的土耳其之行与随后
whether or not there was any quid pro quo involved
你参与起草土耳其军事援助法案间
between your trip to Turkey and your subsequent co-sponsorship
是否存在任何的利益交换
of the military aid bill to that country.
感谢你的直言  议员女士
I appreciate your candor, Congresswoman,
这样我就能直接否认
so I can categorically deny
这二者之间有任何的联系
that there was any connection between the two events.
土耳其之行的目的是在于农业方面
The trip was about agricultural methods.
完毕
Period.
在此次行程中
Did anyone from the Turkish military or government
有任何来自土耳其军方或政府的人与你联系
contact you during your time in Turkey
就军事援助事宜以任何方式进行过讨论吗
to discuss military aid of any nature?
没  他们没有
No, they did not.
所以  这只是个巧合吗
So, it's just a coincidence
所有跟你一起出差的人
that everyone who went on that trip with you
之后都投票赞成军事援助计划
later voted in favor of the military aid package?
沙杜尔议员
Congressman Saldua,
其他279位国会议员
279 other members of Congress
也支持了那项法案  先生
also supported that bill, sir.
通过你的问题来看
And, by your question,
你不仅对我的忠诚表示了怀疑
you are not only impugning my integrity
还责难了我那些再也不能到场
but also that of my colleagues
为自己辩护的同事们
who are no longer here to defend themselves.
这并非我的目的  议长女士
That wasn't my intent, Madame Speaker.
请听我一言
If I may?
虽然你们都是国会新成员
All of you are new to Congress,
但有一点我们是一样的
but one thing we have in common
我们都曾宣誓要维护宪法权威
is the oath we took to uphold the Constitution.
一直以来我竭尽全力践行自己的誓言
I've always done my best to live up to that oath.
也许可供你们查证的真凭实据并不多
There may be little hard evidence here for you to investigate,
但我这一生为公众所尽的义务真切地摆在眼前
but there is a lifetime of public service to consider.
这才是问题的关键所在
And that's what's at stake here.
这也是我最想为自己做的辩护
And that's also my best defense --
以我的功绩和我的名誉之名
my record and my reputation.
到了投票表决的时候
When it comes time to vote...
我希望你们能就此进行投票
I hope you will vote on that.
他们只有一个有用的摄像头
Of course they only have one working camera.
威尔士出来了
There's Wells.
搞什么
The hell?
该死
Damn it.
总统先生
Mr. President.
你们找我吗
You wanted to see me?
是关于威尔士探员的  总统先生
It's about Agent Wells, sir.
她怎么了
What about her?
她被绑架了
She's been kidnapped.
绑架
Kidnapped?
怎么会
How?
昨晚在她住处的停车场内
Last night, in the parking lot of her motel,
一辆货车停下来  那些人把她绑走了
a van pulled up and they grabbed her.
-是谁干的  -我们不知道  总统先生
- Who? - We don't know, sir.
我们追踪了那辆车  但车牌是偷来的
We traced the vehicle, but the plates came back stolen.
-我希望各部门彻查此事  -已经吩咐下去了
- I want every agency on this. - It's already done.
在此之前她在调查什么
What was she closing in on?
她在查布朗宁·里德
She was looking into Browning Reed --
以前的一个军事承包商
a former military contractor.
威尔士探员认为其前任执行董事
Agent Wells is convinced that the ex-C.E.O. Patrick Lloyd's
帕特里克·劳埃德涉嫌参与这起阴谋
involved with the conspiracy.
她掌握了什么证据吗
Did she have any evidence?
迄今为止  这还只是猜想
Right now, it's just a working theory.
我们无法证明他与爆炸案有直接关系
We don't have anything directly tying him to the bombing, yet --
尚未找到任何确凿的证据
no smoking gun.
但我们已对他进行全天候监视
But we've got eyes on him 24/7.
劳埃德住在弗吉尼亚州
Lloyd lives in Virginia,
但最近他一直穿梭于各地
but lately he's been traveling the country,
树立他的政治形象
building up his political profile.
今天下午他要向在市中心集会的极右派发表演说
This afternoon, he's speaking to an alt-right gathering downtown.
利用一切可以利用的资源
Use every resource available to you,
一定要找到威尔士探员
but find Agent Wells.
是的  总统先生
Yes, sir.
还有人买这玩意吗
Some people still buy this stuff, huh?
你让我说什么好呢
What can I say?
赶时髦的人都喜欢模拟信号
Hipsters love analog.
我弄到了定向麦克风和接收器
I got a shotgun mic and receiver.
收音范围达914米
Range of 1,000 yards.
追踪器在里面
The nano tracker inside --
重量完全可以忽略不计
negligible weight difference.
追踪半径为16公里
Tracking radius of 10 miles.
好极了
Perfect.
什么情况
So, what happened?
联调局没玩意可玩了吗
Bureau run out of toys?
谢谢你这么快就能给我搞到这些东西
Thank you for the quick turnaround.
欠你个人情
I owe you.
总统先生  有件事情
Mr. President, I have something
我认为您一定想知道
I think you're going to want to hear.
关于北约峰会
It's about the NATO summit.
洗耳恭听
I'm all ears.
我刚跟新任法国大使见过面
I just came from meeting the new French ambassador,
他想要谈的第一件事就是
and the first thing he wanted to talk about
核弹
was nukes.
核弹怎么了
What about them?
法国自由党几十年来
Liberals in France have been railing against
一直在反对核扩散
nuclear escalation for decades.
但现在  甚至是保守党的人都开始好奇
But now, even the conservatives are beginning to wonder
他们为什么要花那么多钱
why they're spending so much damn money
来维持部署在欧洲的武器
just to maintain weapons in Europe.
布范大使四处暗示
Ambassador Bouvar broadly hinted
他们愿意逐步削减军备  汤姆
that it's an opening to de-escalate, Tom.
好吧
Well, fine,
但要是我没搞错的话
but unless I'm missing something,
如果我们削减军备
if we reduce our arsenal,
有什么能保证我们的敌人不趁机作势呢
what stops our adversaries from taking advantage?
如果西方国家能向俄罗斯展示
If the West could show Russia
我们的确在认真考虑此事
that we were serious about laying down our weapons,
那么他们就可能会觉得削减军备
they might see that it's safe for them
于他们自身也是安全的
to start laying down theirs.
如果他们不这么认为呢
And if they don't?
我们就要一步步来
Well, we'd do it incrementally.
如果无法互惠互利  我们就停止
And if there's no reciprocity, we stop.
但这是个机会
But, it's a chance.
我在任的时候可没有这种机会  总统先生
It's a chance I never got, Mr. President.
不仅要法国和美国同意
It would take more than France and the United States.
-所有盟国都要同意  -当然
- The entire alliance would have to be on-board. - Absolutely.
细节都写在里面了
The details are all in here.
同时  我需要你同意
In the meantime, I will need permission
让我跟法国及另外几个北约成员国
to open any backdoor communication with the French
进行秘密交谈
and a few of our other NATO partners,
而且要立即行动
and we'll have to act fast.
明天的这个时候
This time tomorrow,
大家就要去多伦多参加峰会了
everyone'll be heading to Toronto for the summit.
试试看吧
Let's give it a shot.
是  总统先生
Yes, sir.
谢谢你们
Thank you both.
特伦顿警局十五分钟前打电话说找到了那辆车
Trenton P.D. called in the plate 15 minutes ago.
-空的  -是的  什么都没有
- Empty? - Yeah, top to bottom.
肯定不会给我们留下什么线索
It's not like they're gonna leave us any breadcrumbs.
-她不在里面也是好事  -是的
- Well, it's better than her being in there. - Yeah.
可如果他们抓走她不是为了杀她
But, if they didn't take her to kill her...
那他们抓她是为了什么
Then, what do they want with her?
洛萨诺在哪
Where's Lozano?
跟他说我要跟他谈谈
You tell him I want to talk to him!
我明白  总统先生
I understand, sir.
可问题不是
The problem, though,
民众对这件事的支持
isn't public support for the issue,
而是采矿和公用事业公司
it's the mining and utility companies
在互相争斗
that put up the biggest fight.
本来就不该拿干净的水源来做所谓斗争
Clean water shouldn't even be a fight.
你刚才说的这些公司
These companies that you're talking about
需要为未来考虑
need to start working for the future.
你要知道这些企业高管
You know that business execs
只会考虑最低成本
only think about bottom-line costs.
如果他们只关心成本的话
Well, if their only concern is costs,
那你应该提醒他们处理这个烂摊子要花多少钱
you should remind them how much it costs to clean up their mess,
尤其在我们向他们征收罚款后
especially after we start fining them.
遵命  总统先生
Yes, sir, Mr. President.
谢谢你  布莱恩
Thank you, Brian.
谢谢各位
Thank you all.
金布尔  请随我来
Kimble, please.
听证会怎么样了
So, how did the hearing go?
老实说  我也不知道
Honestly, I don't know.
我觉得我表现得还行
I think I represented myself well.
亚伦也这么觉得
Aaron thought I did.
但那种地方很难摸透
But it's a hard room to read.
你肯定做得很棒
I'm sure you knocked it out of the park.
但总统先生  就算道德委员会没有发现什么问题
But, sir, even if the Ethics Committee finds no wrongdoing,
指控依然存在
the accusation will always be out there.
金布尔
Kimble...
我说过我会支持你
I said I would stand behind you.
-我是认真的  -谢谢  总统先生
- I meant it. - Thank you, sir.
与此同时
In the meantime,
我想要继续工作
I intend to keep doing my job.
公务可不会停止
The business of governing doesn't stop,
就算有道德调查也一样
even for an ethics inquiry.
说到这个
Speaking of which,
我今天早上见到了里士满总统的儿子泰勒
I met with President Richmond's son Tyler this morning.
他跟来自新奥尔良一所高中的
He was with a group of music students
一些学音乐的学生一起来的
from a high school in New Orleans
这所高中是以他父亲的名字命名的
that had just been named after his father.
他跟我说他们学校的音乐项目
Now, he told me that their music program
就要没有资金了
was gonna lose their funding.
你对联邦艺术资助金法案熟不熟
How familiar are you with the federal art grants
能不能帮忙推动此类项目
that make these kind of programs possible?
我记得这个法案
I remember that bill.
为了让我的某些更保守的同事能通过这个法案
The sunset clause was added to get it past
其中还加入了"日落条款"
some of my more conservative colleagues.
国会重新授权拨款
How fast do you think we can get Congress
需要多久
to reauthorize the grant?
我也希望我能帮上你和泰勒  总统先生
I wish I could help you and Tyler with this, sir,
但必须得经过筹款委员会
but it has to go through the Ways and Means Committee,
而委员会的主席是欧文·沙杜尔
which is chaired by Owen Saldua,
他正好是道德委员会中负责调查
who just happens to be leading the charge against me
-对我的指控的人  -你开玩笑吧
- in the Ethics Committee. - You're kidding me.
很遗憾  并不是
Unfortunately, no.
目前我无法对他施加影响
I don't have any leverage with him right now.
但你或许有
But you might.
沙杜尔是无党派人士
Saldua's an Independent.
他可能会听你的
He might just listen to you.
好吧  我会联系他
Okay, I'll reach out to him.
柯克曼夫人  谢谢你今天带我们参观
Thanks again, Mrs. Kirkman, for showing us around today.
别客气  叫我艾丽克斯就好
No, no, please, call me Alex.
这很棒  也让我很开心
It was great, and it made me happy.
那些孩子们
Those kids,
对他们做的事情都充满了热情
they're so passionate about what they're doing,
他们还很崇拜你
and they adore you.
他们能让我跟着  我已经很幸运了
Well, I'm just lucky they let me hang around.
拜托
Come on.
别那么谦虚
Don't sell yourself short.
看得出来你跟他们关系很融洽
I could tell you have a way with them.
对我来说也受益匪浅
Well, it's -- it's been good for me, too.
你最近怎么样
How are you doing?
孩子们都挺不错的
The kids are good... really.
住进总统行宫算是个改变
Camp David's been a change.
佩妮倒还好
Not so much for Penny
因为她视所有事情都为一种挑战
because, you know, she sees everything as an adventure...
但是李奥  我觉得他认为我们在惩罚他
But Leo, I-I think he thinks we're punishing him.
是的
Yeah.
陷入这里
Well, I know how hard it can be,
我知道有多么难受
you know, being a part of all this.
这甚至都不是你所要求的
And you didn't even sign up for it.
你也没有
Well, neither did you,
但是你似乎应对得非常好
but you seemed to cope really well.
我想这对谁来说都不是易事  对吗
I-I guess it's -- it's not easy for anyone, right?
我以前希望我的孩子们可以拥有非凡的人生
I used to want my kids to have extraordinary lives.
现在我只想
And now I-I just...
我只想他们简单平凡就好
I just want some semblance of ordinary, you know.
从我的经验来看
From, um, my experience,
孩子们会触底反弹的
kids can bounce back from a lot.
重要的是你们要团结在一起
What matters is, is that you stick together.
我们会带领美国重振雄风
这边请  劳埃德先生  借过
Right this way, Mr. Lloyd. Excuse me.
谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
走过金属探测门之前
Place all metal objects in the tray
-请把所有金属物品放入盒内  -好的
- before stepping through the metal detector. - Okay.
先生  您的胸针
Sir, your lapel pin.
-你在开玩笑对吗  -机器非常敏感
- You're kidding, right? - It's a very sensitive machine.
-好吧  -谢谢
- Okay. - Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
小菜一碟
Easy like Sunday morning.
给你点小费
Just a little tip.
谢谢
Thanks.
你想要吗
Want it?
不  你留着吧
Nah, you can keep it.
谢谢
Thanks.
沙杜尔议员来了
Congressman Saldua's here.
议员  欢迎来到白宫
Congressman, welcome to the White House.
-请坐  -谢谢您  这是我的荣幸
- Please. - Thank you, sir. It's an honor.
我以前一直希望我可以尽早拿到邀请
I was hoping I might get an invitation soon,
但是考虑到目前的情况
though I am a bit wary about coming in today,
对于今天是否来拜访我还是心存顾虑
given the circumstances.
我并非要干预正在进行的调查
I'm not here to meddle in any ongoing investigations,
我也十分抱歉
and I am very sorry
我们一直没有机会见面
that we haven't had the chance to meet yet.
我还在摸索我的从政之路
I'm still trying to find my way around here,
正如你一样
as I'm sure you are.
每天如此  总统先生
Every day, Mr. President.
但是我相信我们可以大展拳脚
But I'm convinced we can do some great work.
很高兴能听你这么说
That's good to hear.
还有很多工作要做
There's a lot of work to do.
今天我在思考教育的事
Today, I was thinking about education.
我见了新奥尔良州的一些高中生
I met some high school students from New Orleans --
一部分音乐项目是由
part of a music program funded by
全国艺术基金会资助的
the National Endowment for the Arts.
但是不幸的是
But, unfortunately,
他们的资金快要用完了
their funding's about to run out.
艺术教育是我们筹措到下一笔预算之后
Arts education is certainly something to look at
必须去关注的板块
as we approach the next budget.
这些孩子等不了那么久
These kids can't wait that long.
他们的拨款下个月到期
Their grant expires next month
除非国会可以再次通过
unless Congress re-approves it.
所以我想也许我们可以
So, I was hoping that maybe
想一个特事特办的方法
we could find a way to fast-track it --
把它附加到其他项目中去
tack it on to something else.
恕我无礼  先生
Respectfully, sir,
我在国会的工作
I ran for Congress
就是要阻断这种暗箱操作
to avoid that kind of back-room dealing.
恕我无礼  这不是什么暗箱
Respectfully, this isn't a back room.
这里是白宫总统办公室
This is the Oval Office of the White House.
这种幕后操手正是华盛顿几十年来
These kind of riders have been part of the problem
一直存在的一类问题
in Washington for decades.
你帮帮我  我帮帮你
I mean, you scratch my back, I scratch yours.
议员先生
Congressman,
这个项目影响的不仅是新奥尔良的高中学生
this won't just affect high school students in New Orleans.
这是全国性项目
This is a national program.
-后果将会  -我和大家一样热爱音乐
- The ramifications... - Look, I love music as much as anyone.
但许多民众认为
But a lot of folks think
应该把所有精力
we should throw everything we've got
花在发展科技  工程  数学等学科上
into science, technology, engineering, math.
以往美国在这些领域首屈一指
We used to lead the world in those areas.
而现在我们只能算是中等水平了
Now, we're barely in the middle of the pack.
我觉得我们的孩子
I don't think our children
不该被迫在艺术与科学之间做选择
should be forced to choose between art or science.
总统先生  如果我们能筹措出这笔预算
I'm happy to debate this, Mr. President,
我很乐意支持这个立场
when we put together the next budget.
今年是清算之年
This is the year of our reckoning.
世界上的其他国家就快要追赶上
The rest of the world is catching up to what we've known --
我们长久以来的成就了
that for far too long,
政府想要绑架我们的身份
government has tried to hijack our identities,
控制我们的生活  给我们的孩子洗脑
control our lives, and brainwash our children.
但以后再也不会了
But no longer.
因为我们正在崛起
No longer because we are rising up.
-没错  -是的
-Yeah! -Yeah!
这次运动是我们国家的未来
This movement is the future of our nation,
没有非法的政府
and no -- no illegitimate government,
没有非法的总统
no illegitimate president,
能阻挡我们
is going to stand in our way.
德尔顿
Dalton.
我是法索
It's Foerstel.
劳埃德怎么样
How's Lloyd?
正在总结他的啤酒馆暴动宣言
Just wrapping up his Beer Hall Putsch.
真是鼓舞人心  随时向我汇报
Inspiring. Keep me posted.
雷伯恩众议院办公楼
不是吧  哥哥  这是我第一周上班
Come on, man. It's my first week.
你就来找我套消息了吗
You're already shaking me down?
不然兄妹是用来干嘛的
Well, what else are cousins for, right?
我又不是让你泄露
Come on, I'm not asking for any state secrets
国家秘密之类的东西
or anything like that.
我只是想知道
I just want to know what your take
今天早上听证会情况有多糟
was on how things went down this morning.
我知道吉田议员很是感动
I know Congresswoman Yoshida was impressed.
然后呢
Okay?
还有德拉克罗瓦和哈蒙
And Delacroix and Harmon, too.
什么  只有这几个吗
What, that's it?
我们拿到的支持只有这么点
We didn't get more support than that?
我是说  还有一些听证成员没联系完
I mean, they still have more witnesses to call.
所以你认为票数是九比三  是吗
So, you think it's gonna be a 9-3 against.
好吧
Yeah, all right.
我是说  我可能有错
I mean, I could be wrong.
有什么风声我会告诉你的
I'll call you if I hear anything.
谢谢你
Thank you.
抱歉  表哥
九比三吗
9 to 3 against?
只是估计而已  议长女士
It's an estimate, ma'am.
他们还有别的证人要传唤
They still have other witnesses to call.
是啊  官僚主义者总是只简单确认已知事实
Yeah, bureaucrats who simply confirm the facts they already know.
我出了趟差以及法案被通过
I took a trip and there was a bill.
其他人还是可能改变主意的
Well, the others can still change their minds.
我以为自己做得比这更好的
I thought I did better than that.
你做得很好  议长女士
No, you did fine, ma'am.
这是个非正规法庭
This is a kangaroo court.
他们会免除我的议长职务
They're going to strip me of my Speakership.
仅凭他们之力无法罢免你
And they can't do that alone.
他们只能向众议院提出建议
They can only recommend to the full House.
你还可以抗争
You can still fight this.
用什么来抗争
With what?
事实无法改变
The facts won't change.
今天与委员会的会面  我已尽了全力
I gave it my best shot in there today with the committee.
为什么你觉得面对众议院之时  情况能更好
What makes you think I'll do any better in the House?
因为这样我们就有时间组织公关活动了
Because it'll give us time to organize a campaign.
将你的资料向全国媒体公布
We'll put your profile out there in the national media,
我们尽量拖延这件事
We'll drag it out as long as we can...
直到公众舆论
until public opinion
转向你这一方
swings the vote in your direction.
你可能给我出了个主意  亚伦
You may have just given me an idea, Aaron.
什么
For what?
最后一搏
A last hurrah.
谢谢你今天能过来
Thank you for coming today.
谢谢  谢谢  很高兴认识你
Thank you. Thank you. It's good to see you.
目标正在离开
Target on the way out.
收到  准备移动
On it. Ready to move.
距离
238米
我们将各项信息浓缩成几个要点
We'll boil the message down to a handful of talking points,
然后于峰会前
get those out to some key media outlets
通报各大重要媒体
in anticipation of the summit,
您之后在多伦多的讲话将建立于此基础上
and then your speech in Toronto will build on those.
少点国家主义  增加多邦合作
Less nationalism, more multinationalism.
这就是要点所在
Well, that's the gist of it.
在减少全球范围内的
And let's be specific
军事热区问题上  我们要明确点
about reducing military hot spots around the globe.
-建立意识  -好主意
- Build awareness. - Good idea.
-我准备好草稿以便您在飞机上看  -谢谢
- I'll have a draft for you to read on the plane. - Thank you.
我就艺术教育拨款问题
Sir, I, uh -- I've reached out to Leg Affairs
联系了立法事务局的人
about that arts education grant.
-有进展吗  -他们正在努力
- Any luck? - They're trying,
但看起来沙杜尔议员
but it seems Congressman Saldua
在众议院里的财权掌控得比较严
controls the purse strings in the House pretty tightly.
大多数代表都没有投票经历  很难说话
Most of these new reps don't have any voting history to speak of,
所以我们要自己摸索了
so we're feeling our way in the dark.
但我要了一份名单  名单上每个选举区
But I did request a list of every Congressional district
-至少有一所学校参与该项目  -很好
- with at least one school in the program. - Good.
这也许能让他们再仔细考虑一下
That might make them think twice,
让他们知道如果停止拨款
knowing they're gonna have to face their constituents
他们就要面对自己的选民了
if they let the grant expire.
-谢谢  -先别说谢谢
- Thank you. - Don't thank me yet.
我还在努力呢
I'm still working on it.
我在听证会上说什么并不重要  对吗
It really didn't matter what I said in that hearing, did it?
你知道我不能讨论仍在进行中的道德调查
You know I can't discuss an ongoing ethics investigation,
尤其对方是当事人
especially not with its subject.
我也知道你想踢我出局  欧文
I also know you want me out, Owen.
我相信你所代表的政治活动
I believe the kind of politicking you represent
应该已经成为过去了
should be a thing of the past.
我明白这对于传递消息有好处
I understand that's good for messaging,
但是关于我们老派政客有一点你不了解
but what you don't realize about us old-school politicians
我们明白这些程序
is that we understand procedure.
如果这些上交到众议院
If this goes to the House,
至少接下来六个月
I could eat up the next six months at least
我会被听证会  动议
with hearings and motions
和传讯所吞噬
and subpoenas.
-这是威胁吗  -不是
- Is that a threat? - No.
其实恰恰相反
Quite the opposite, actually.
我愿意给你让路
I'm willing to get out of your way.
你说什么
I'm sorry?
我想为国家着想
I want what's best for the country.
所以我会退位让贤
So, I'll step aside,
辞去议长职位
resign the Speakership,
以及我的位置
and my seat.
我承认
I'll admit.
我很惊讶
I'm surprised.
但我想你做一件事  欧文
But I want something from you, Owen.
在我走之前  我希望公众艺术教育
I want the public arts education funding reauthorized
再次获得批准
before I go.
这项行动仍然有可行性
The operation is still viable.
现在  我会清除你
Right now, I'm brooming any connection
布朗宁·里德以及国会任务之间的联系
between you, Browning Reed, and the Capitol mission.
那我想知道
Well, then, I want to know why
为什么两名联调局调查员来调查我的物业
two federal investigators were on my property.
这你别担心  我会去查
Don't worry about it. I'm on it.
000034音频
很快  就不会再有书面记录等等的问题
Soon, there'll be no paper trail whatsoever,
而且威尔士探员已被抓获
and Agent Wells is contained.
好
Okay.
那媒体方面呢
Well, what about the, uh -- the press angle?
埃布·莱纳德的一切都步入了正轨
Everything's on track with Abe Leonard.
我给他的一切  他都消化了
He's eaten up everything I've fed him.
他以为自己会成为揭发水门事件的记者
He thinks he's another Woodward and Bernstein.
那我们什么时候能看到他采取行动
Well, when are we going to see something from him, then?
应该快了
Any day, I expect.
你确定联调局不会发现任何端倪吗
And you're sure that the FBI has no idea what's coming.
所有的调查局现在都专注于
All the agencies are focused on
布鲁克硬盘上的三个目标
the three targets from Brooke's hard drive --
金门大桥  胡佛水坝
the Golden Gate Bridge, the Hoover Dam,
以及自由女神像
and the Statue of Liberty.
-控制权在我们手里  -那就好
- We have operational control. - Good.
杰伊
Jay...
我们就快接近了
we are so close.
我们也许没有总统地位
We might not have the Presidency,
但可以十分肯定  不久以后
but you can be damn sure that, before long,
我们就能掌控整个国家
we will have the country.
我已经调查过
I've done a multi-agency document search
任何含有白宫
for any files with the words
及布朗宁·里德字眼的多家机构文件
"White House" and "Browning Reed" in them.
我设法找到的只有这些
All I've managed to find was this.
只有五个文件
It's, like, five files.
-这怎么可能  -可能是有人
- How's that possible? - Someone would've had to physically
在西翼手动清理了这些文件
remove these documents from the West Wing.
那肯定会有数字记录的
Well, there's got to be a digital record.
还在搜索数据库
Still poring through the database.
似乎自从国会袭击案之后
And it seems since the attack at the Capitol,
提及到布朗宁·里德的文件
references to Browning Reed
都被系统删除了
have been systematically deleted.
有人想掩盖他们的踪迹
Someone's covering their tracks.
如果我们找到删除文件的人...
If we find out who deleted these files...
我们就找到了叛徒
We find our traitor.
我跟泰勒·里士满聊了很久
I had a long talk with Tyler Richmond.
他有个让人心疼的地方  你知道吗
There was just this sadness about him, you know?
他一点都不了解他父亲
He didn't get to know his dad growing up --
全部的政治观点还有白宫
all the politics and then the White House,
我觉得他仍在追赶他的父亲
and I felt like he's still chasing his father.
我不想我们的孩子变成这样
I so don't want that for our kids.
我也不想
I don't want it either.
我知道我们是在保护他们
I know we're trying to protect them,
但他们跟我们一起不是更好吗
but aren't they better off with us --
和我们两个一起
both of us?
现在还不是时候
Not yet.
我  我很抱歉  但
I'm -- I'm sorry, but...
我也很抱歉
Well, me too.
汤姆...
Tom...
谁
Yes?
总统先生  霍斯拉滕议长来了
Sir, Speaker Hookstraten?
等我一下
Just give me a second.
你先工作吧
I'll let you get back to your work.
艾丽克斯...
Alex...
没关系  我们迟点再聊
No, we'll talk later.
金布尔  来  请坐
Kimble, please, have a seat.
你跟委员会那边聊过了吗
Did you speak with the committee?
私底下聊过
Unofficially.
我想尽快跟你谈谈
And I wanted to speak to you as soon as possible.
什么事
What is it?
我决定了要辞职
I've decided to resign.
议长职位吗
The Speakership?
还有我的席位
And my seat.
什么
What?
金布尔  这样做没有任何意义
Kimble, that doesn't make any sense.
道德委员会准备要投票反对我  先生
The Ethics Committee is going to vote against me, sir,
他们要向白宫建议
recommend to the House
开除我议长的职位
that I be removed as Speaker.
你在白宫还有盟友呀
You have friends in the House.
不够的
Not enough.
不管怎样
For better or worse,
对于新国会来说我代表着旧的那一套
I represent old politics to a new Congress.
这就是新的政治吗
And this is the new politics?
这是扫清障碍
This is a purge.
我说过我会战斗到最后一刻
I said I would fight till the end,
我觉得现在是时候了
and I can see now that this is it.
我当初来华盛顿是为了服务国家
I came to Washington to serve,
但我却不能像我保证的那样
but I can't represent my constituents
代表我的选民
the way they deserve.
金布尔  求你了
Kimble, please.
告诉我能做些什么
Tell me what I can do.
你什么都做不了
Nothing.
我们也无能为力
It's out of our hands.
但我至少还有个小小的好消息
But, I do have a little bit of good news, at least.
是我作为议长所做的最后贡献
As my last act as Speaker,
议会会继续资助艺术教育经费
the House will refinance the arts education funding
给罗伯特·里士满高中
for Robert Richmond High
以及依靠这笔经费的公立学校
and all the other public schools that depend on it.
怎么可能
How is that even possible?
沙杜尔说他绝不同意
Saldua said he'd never do it.
每个犯人都有最后一餐
Well, every inmate gets a last meal.
我只是要求了一点肉
I asked for a little bit of pork.
总统先生  你是我在华盛顿
You know, you're the best ally
得到的最好的盟友
I could've ever hoped for in Washington, sir.
很荣幸和你共事
It's been an honor serving with you.
不
No.
你说什么
I'm sorry?
我不接受
I won't accept this.
我很欣赏你的姿态  总统先生
I appreciate the gesture, Mr. President,
但是我们不能寄希望于国会
but we can't take on Congress.
我在考虑寄希望于其他的东西
I'm thinking of taking on something else.
不行妈妈  只有总统
No, Mom, only the president gets to wave
在登上空军一号的时候可以挥手
when he steps on Air Force One.
我是不能嘚瑟的
I don't get a shout-out.
这又不是超级碗
This is not the Super Bowl.
我得挂了
I-- hey, uh, I got to go.
我会带厚衣服的
Yes, I'm bringing warm clothing.
-我爱你  再见  -我爱你
- Okay, I love you too, bye.  - Oh, love you, too.
-谁啊  -北约会议演练而已
- Who's that? - Uh, just some NATO prep.
你知道空军一号上的食物
Hey, did you know that they charge you
是要收钱的吗
for the food on Air Force One
吃不吃都要收钱
whether you actually eat it or not?
那你知不知道
Yeah, well, did you know
抱怨空军一号上的食物这种行为
that complaining about the meals on Air Force One
就跟告诉别人
is the same thing as telling people
你看不上波士顿的学校一样
you went to school outside of Boston?
哈佛大学  麻省理工等五所名校皆位于波士顿
-剑桥就不在波士顿  -老天
- Cambridge is outside of Boston. - Oh, my God.
我确定你很快就有机会
Look, I'm sure you'll ride on the plane
坐那个飞机了
soon enough, right?
总得有人镇守大局
Somebody's got to stay here to hold down the fort.
好吧  希望你喜欢飞机上的脆饼干
Oh, well, I hope you enjoy your in-flight pretzels
因为到时候我就是整个白宫
because I will be the highest ranking person
职务最高的人了
in the White House.
真可怕
That's terrifying.
告诉我你已经找到她了
Tell me that you found her.
只是时间问题
It's only a matter of time, sir.
我们会找到她的
We will find her.
我们有了新发现
But, there is a new development.
我们找到方法锁定叛徒了
We think there's a way to identify the traitor
通过追踪电脑痕迹
through a computer trace.
会很艰难  但是会有结果的
It's gonna be pain-staking, but it will get results.
与此同时
And in the meantime, sir,
我们得谈谈你明天的行程
we need to discuss your trip tomorrow.
我不认为你现在
I don't think it's a good idea
离开白宫是个好主意
for you to leave the White House right now.
麦克  我理解你的担忧
Mike, I understand your concerns,
但我必须得去
but I have to go.
我不会退缩
I'm not pulling out.
那么我坚持还要加倍安保
Then I insist we increase your security even more.
你认为有必要就行
Do whatever you think is necessary.
但如果我们就快找出叛徒了
But, if we're this close to finding the traitor,
我希望你留在华盛顿
I want you here in Washington.
-先生  我  -总统说得很对
- Sir, I--  - Wait, no, the president's right.
我们人手太过于分散
We're spread way too thin as it is.
只有四个人了解全部情况
There's only four of us who know the full extent of this,
有三个都在这间房间里
and three of us are in this room.
总统先生  你的安全仍是我第一要务
Mr. President, your safety is still my primary directive.
那由你来亲自挑选我的安保人员
Then you handpick my detail.
你信任他们的话  我就信任
If you trust them, I trust them.
但我想让你留在这
But, I want you here.
谢谢
Thank you.
遵命
Yes, sir.
我够不到
I can't reach it.
谢谢
Thank you.
我都以为你要放我鸽子了
I was starting to wonder if you'd stood me up.
过来
Come here.
怎么了
What is it?
没事
Nothing.
是因为我之前说的话吗
Is it about what I said earlier?
不  我保证不是
No. No, I promise.
我只是思绪很乱
I just got a lot on my mind.
来  咱们去做准备
Come on, let's get ready.
汤姆  我很担心你
Tom, I'm worried about you.
我能从你脸色看出来
I can see it in your face --
这份工作对你产生了负面影响
the toll this job is taking on you.
我知道你不能把所有的事情都告诉我
I mean, I know you can't tell me everything,
但你可以告诉我一些的
but you can tell me something.
如果我帮不到你
If I can't help you,
那我在这里的意义又是什么呢
then what's the point of me even being here?
我派了人去帮我做一件事
I asked someone to do something for me...
一件很危险的事...
...something very dangerous...
可能会让他们失去生命
...and it might cost them their life.
我当初在高中时参加合唱团时
When I was in choir in high school,
就从未被邀请到白宫表演过
we were never invited to the White House.
我们也是
Neither were we.
-你还参加过合唱团  -魔术社
- You were in choir? - Magic club.
现在想想  我们就没被邀请表演过
We never got invited anywhere, now that I think of it.
你确定你能行吗
Are you sure you're up for this?
不  我想出席
No, I want to be here.
-泰勒  你好吗  -总统先生
- Tyler, how are you? - Mr. President.
柯克曼夫人
Mrs. Kirkman.
孩子们怎么样
How are the kids?
他们有点紧张
They're a little nervous.
毕竟这不是学校礼堂
This isn't exactly their high school auditorium.
怎么会  他们一定会表现得很棒
Oh, come on. They're gonna be great.
这会让他们永生难忘的
And they're gonna remember this forever.
我想第一个告诉你
I wanted to be the first to tell you.
国会将重新批准拨款
Congress is gonna reauthorize the grant.
-真的吗  -真的
- You serious? - Yes.
你应该感谢金布尔·霍斯拉滕
You should thank Kimble Hookstraten.
这件事是她促成的
She's the one who made it happen.
不用担心  亚伦
Don't worry, Aaron.
这不再与沙杜尔议员有关了
It's not about Congressman Saldua anymore.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen
有请总统先生
the President of the United States.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢  不用鼓掌了
Thank you, please.
感谢大家的出席
Thank you all for joining us.
我知道你们今天到场
I know that you did not come here today
不是来听我的声音的
to listen to my voice,
所以我会尽量简短发言
so I will make this as brief as possible.
你们即将欣赏的演出  将由来自新奥尔良州
The performance that you are about to hear will be given by
最近更名为罗伯特·里士满高中的
the student choir and orchestra of the newly renamed
学生合唱团与交响乐团带来
Robert Richmond High School of New Orleans.
与他们一同出席的是泰勒·里士满
And with them today is Tyler Richmond --
他自己就是天赋异禀的音乐家
a talented musician himself
也不遗余力地提倡艺术教育
and a great advocate for education in the arts.
今天早些时候
Earlier today,
泰勒提醒了我艺术是社会的命脉
Tyler reminded me that art is the lifeblood of society.
在努力为每个在美国的学子
And as we strive to create a truly comprehensive education
创造一个真正综合的教育体系的过程中
for every student in America,
我越发明确地意识到
I realize now more than ever
我们需要一个有能力有激情的人
that we need someone who is capable and passionate
来统领全局
to lead the charge.
在此  我认为没有更好的场合
Now, I can't think of a better setting
来宣布我的教育部长人选
to announce my nominee for Secretary of Education than this.
那么  我来骄傲地介绍
So, it is with great pride that I introduce
金布尔·霍斯拉滕议长
Speaker Kimble Hookstraten.
谢谢  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
很荣幸与你在国会共事
It's been an honor to work with you in Congress.
很荣幸能为了
And it will be my honor to fight beside you
我们的孩子的教育并肩作战
for the education of our children.
未来各界的领袖
Future leaders in every field,
这份工作是为了孩子们
this job is about our kids,
这个下午也是
and this afternoon is, too.
所以  我也很荣幸
So, it is also my honor
欢迎来自罗伯特·里士满高中的
to welcome the student orchestra
学生乐团
of Robert Richmond High School.
♪Wade in the water♪
♪Children♪
♪Wade in the water, children♪
♪Wade, wade, wade♪  ♪Wade in the water♪
♪God's gonna trouble the water♪
谢谢
Thank you.
先生
Sir.
我第一次乘空军一号
It's my first time on Air Force One.
让我来
Well, here, let me.
您不必这样做  先生
Oh, you don't have to do that, sir.
-没事  我知道怎么用这些东西  -好吧
- No, no, I know how to work these things. - All right.
实际上
As a matter of fact, uh,
你还不如拍张好照片
you might as well just do it right.
爬上楼梯
Go on up those stairs.
-汤姆  拍一张  -不
- Here, Tom, take a -- - No.
和赛斯拍张照
...take a picture with Seth.
赛斯  上来
Seth, come on up here!
没关系的  先生  您不必这样做
That's okay, sir. You don't have to do that.
为什么不呢  快去
Why not? Go ahead. Well, uh...
这...
This is, uh --
这只是发我妈妈的照片  先生
this is just a photo for my mom, sir.
不是  不是为了发上网或者什么的
It's not -- not for Instagram or anything like that.
准备好了吗
You ready?
等等
Uh, wait.
我可以招手吗
Uh, can I wave?
-我妈肯定会喜欢的  -招手吧
- My mom would really like that. - Wave away.
拍好了
Got it.
上飞机吧
Come on aboard.
谢谢
Thank you.
这可不是食物
That's not food.